xpressdocs.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy

Xpressdocs knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Xpressdocs´ website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

  * What personal information does the Xpressdocs website gather?
  * What about cookies?
  * Does the Xpressdocs website share the information it receives?
  * How secure is information about me?
  * Which information can I access?
  * What choices do I have?
  * Conditions of use, notices, and revisions

## What personal information does the Xpressdocs website gather?

**Information you or your company gives us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information; however, this may limit you from taking advantage of many of the website’s features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future ordering for you, improving our service and communicating with you.

**Automatic information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses the **Xpressdocs** website. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit websites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at the **Xpressdocs** website if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.

**E-mail communications:** To help us make the e-mails we send you more useful and informative, we may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from the **Xpressdocs** website if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other forms of communication from us, please contact us and let us know your wishes.

**Information from other sources:** We may receive information about you from other sources and add it to your account information. Depending on the level of integration, your information may be supplied by integration with your company’s intranet system or your intranet provider’s system, or it may be supplied as raw data from one or more of these sources with prior authorization from the company.

Back to Top » 

## What about "cookies"?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide various features within the system. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, we cannot guarantee that your browsing and shopping experience will be optimal, or functional for that matter, so we suggest you at the least accept cookies originating from our website.

Back to Top » 

## Does the Xpressdocs website share the information it receives?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others.

**Financial processing:** We use Authorize.net for our credit card processing. Authorize.net is a reputable and well recognized financial processing company. Information required to process a credit card transaction (such as name, address, credit card number, etc.) is securely transmitted to [Authorize.net](http://www.authorize.net/) for payment authorization and processing. For information on Authorize.net’s security and privacy policies, please visit their website at [www.authorize.net](http://www.authorize.net/). 

**Agents and customer service:** We do not employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. This means that whenever and however you contact **Xpressdocs** you will be communicating with an employee of **Xpressdocs**. Consequently, such communication will always be bound by the conditions listed in this Privacy Policy. Back to Top » 

## How secure is information about me?

We work to protect the security of the information that is transmitted to us while you are using the **Xpressdocs** website. We do this by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card number(s) when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to [Authorize.net](http://www.authorize.net/) during order processing.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Whenever you are using a shared computer, be sure to sign off from the website once you have finished using it.

Back to Top » 

## Which information can I access?

The **Xpressdocs** website gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with the **Xpressdocs** website for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.

Back to Top » 

## What choices do I have regarding sharing my information with the **Xpressdocs** website?

As discussed elsewhere on this page, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of the Xpressdocs website features and services.

If you do not want to receive e-mail or other communication from us, please contact us, and we will ensure that you receive no more communications from us. 

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable cookies altogether. Please note that you will not be able to use important features of the **Xpressdocs** website if you do not use cookies.

Back to Top » 

## Conditions of use, notices, and revisions

If you choose to visit the **Xpressdocs** website, your visit and any dispute over privacy, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Texas, is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Conditions of Use. If you have any concern about privacy at the **Xpressdocs** website, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Policy will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our Privacy Policy and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to. Even so, you should check our website frequently to learn about recent changes, if any. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make and will never materially change our Privacy Policy to make it less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

Back to Top »
